W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- 1968 Official files, 1968 - 1971; F-55-43; 11 cm of textual records
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Press releases, financial statistics, letters, telegrams, reports. Letters from: John E. Wiley, J.R. South, Jack West, C.E. Medland, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Letters, printed material, report. Letters from: C.L. Goddard, C.D. Sheppard, George McLean, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters. Letters from: J.S. Broadbent, Wesley D. Black, R.A. Switzer, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Provincial Secretary--B.C. Medical Plan (29-4) - Letters, regulations. Letters from: G.A. Stewart, R.G. Wilson, E.C. McCoy, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Letters, report. Letters from: W. Ross Thatcher, Grace McCarthy, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1968; F-55-43-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
- 1969 Official files, 1969 - 1972; F-55-44; 16 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1969. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Hydro, Education, Federal Departments, Federal-Provincial Conferences, Finance, Industrial Development, B.C. Medical Plan and Premiers' Conference. Included are correspondence with Members elected in 1969, other correspondence, reports, press releases, financial statistics and financial statements.
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Letters, reports. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, Einar M. Gunderson, Hugh L. Keenleyside, William C. Mearns, Thomas Chambers, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Cariboo Member--Alex V. Fraser (5-2) - Letters, telegram. Letters from: Alex V. Fraser, 1971 - 1972; F-55-44-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Education--Deputy and Department (9-2) - Press release, financial statistics, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Letters. Letters from: Eric Kierans, Henry F. Davis, John H. Young, John Munro, Walter Weir, Ron Basford, Jean Chretien, Pierre Elliott Trudeau, John P. Robarts, John N. Turner, E.J. Benson, Otto Lang, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Letters. Letters from: Paul Yuzyk, E. Gallant, Leslie R. Peterson, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-67)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Letters, telegrams, reports. Letters from: C.E. Blaney, Leslie R. Peterson, Walter Weir, Pierre Elliott Trudeau, Eric Kierans, Ron Basford, Henry F. Davis, Otto Lang, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters, financial statements. Letters from: C.E. Medland, W.P. Wright, John E. Wiley, O.V. Cecil, Michael J. Wheaton, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Industrial Development Trade and Commerce--Review of Economic and Business Activity (16-5) - Financial statistics, computer printouts, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Provincial Secretary--B.C. Medical Plan (29-4) - Letters. Letters from: G.A. Stewart, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Letters, telegrams, statement. Letters from: J. Bertrand, G.B. McLean, E.J. Benson, Pierre Elliott Trudeau, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Revelstoke Member--Burt Campbell (SC) (31-3) - Letters, telegrams, clippings. Letters from: Burt Campbell, Arvid W. Lundell, 1969 - 1972; F-55-44-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Social Credit League, B.C. (34-2) - Statement, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1969; F-55-44-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
- 1970 Official files, 1970 - 1972; F-55-45; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1970. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Hydro, Finance, Speaker, Premiers' Conference and Social Credit. Included are correspondence, financial statistics, file notes, lists, balance sheets, agendas and speeches.
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Letters, financial statistics. Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, Einar M. Gunderson, J. Toran, C.W. Nash, A. Leckie, H.N. Lash, 1970; F-55-45-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-68)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters. Letters from: W. Joseph Wilson, R.K. Wright, G.S. Bryson, Jan A. Luven, F.B.C. Tice, Bill Wilder, Robert W. Wadds, Nigel H. Gunn, Edward H. Gunn, J.M.G. Scott, 1970; F-55-45-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Legislature--Speaker and Clerk (20-1) - Letters, file notes, lists. Letters from: E. George MacMinn, John R. Nicholson, 1970; F-55-45-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Legislature--Speaker and Clerk (20-1) - Letters, file notes, lists, invitations. Letters from: Gerald H. Cross, E.K. DeBeck, W.H. Murray, Evan Wolfe, John R. Nicholson, E. George MacMinn. (Originally in above file.), 1971 - 1972; F-55-45-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Letters. Letters from: Edward Schreyer, Robert Bourassa, 1970; F-55-45-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Social Credit League, B.C. (34-2) - Letters, balance sheets, proposals. Letters from: Isabel P. Dawson, Vera M. Moffat, Esther W. Hall, Patrick A. Jacox, George Driediger, Gladys Schoor, John Wolff, 1970 - 1972; F-55-45-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Social Credit League--Federal (34-3) - Letters, agendas. Letters from: F.D. Marion, J. Martin Hattersley, C.V. Hutton, Gilbert Rondeau, Real Caouette, Herbert Watson, Nicholas Zambus, 1970 - 1971; F-55-45-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1970; F-55-45-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
- 1971 Official files, F-55-46; 20 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1971. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Hydro, B.C. Energy Board, C.B.C., Federal Departments, Federal-Provincial Conferences, Finance, Oil Pipeline and Premiers' Conference. Included are correspondence, file notes, schedules, memoranda, reports and speeches.
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Letters, file notes, document (photocopy). Letters from: Gordon M. Shrum, Einar M. Gunderson, G.A. Woodbury, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - B.C. Energy Board (3-1) - Letters, file notes. Letters from: J.J. Southworth, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - C.B.C. (5-1) - Letters, schedules. Letters from: Claudette Lenihan, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-69)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Letters, telegrams, memoranda. Letters from: Robert Andras, E.J. Benson, Eric Kierans, John N. Turner, Pierre Elliot Trudeau, Jack Davis, James A. Richardson, Jean-Luc Pepin, Don Jamieson, Charles MacNaughton, Graham Scott, Robert Stanbury, Jean Chretien, Mitchell Sharp, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-70)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Letters, press release, telegrams, guidelines. Letters from: Norah Michener, Robert Andras, Gerard Pelletier, Edward Schreyer, E.J. Benson, Pierre Elliott Trudeau, Bryce Mackasey, Henry F. Davis, Don Jamieson, Mitchell Sharp, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-70)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Letters. Letters from: Pierre Elliott Trudeau, Claire L. McLaughlin, John N. Turner, Henry F. Davis, W.H. Murray, John H. Wood, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-70)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences--Constitutional Conference (10-1) - Reports, letters, reference manual. Letters from: Pierre Elliott Trudeau, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-70)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences--Constitutional Conference (10-1) - Reports, press releases, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-70)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters. Letters from: Samuel F. Hughes, W. Leach, John I. Ross, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Legislature--Speaker and Clerk (20-1) - Report, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - LO-LZ (21) - Letters. Letters from: Denys Lowson, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: W.O. Twaits, George A. Bevan, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Peace River Constituency Associations--Social Credit League, B.C. (28-1) - Letters, proposal. Letters from: Donald A. Marshall, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Letters, statement. Letters from: Richard B. Hatfield, Harry E. Strom, Edward Schreyer, William G. Davis, Joseph R. Smallwood, Michael J.L. Kirby, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Rehabilitation and Social Improvement--Minister (31-5) - Letter (photocopy), 1971; F-55-46-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, 1971; F-55-46-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
- 1972 Official files, 1958 - 1972; F-55-47; 21 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1972. The records reflect topics such as B.C. Hydro, Elections, Federal-Provincial Conferences, Finance, Health Services, Highways, Premier's Office, B.C. Medical Plan and Premiers' Conference. Included are correspondence, a petition, financial statistics and speeches. Photocopied Premier's Office file lists are included at the end of this series.
  - AA-AL (1) - Letters, speech. Letters from: F.H. Peacock, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - B.C. Hydro and Power Authority (3-1) - Letters. Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, Gordon M. Shrum, Thomas Chambers, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Bennett, Hon. W.A.C. and Mrs.--Hon. Membership, Patronage, etc. (3-5) - Letters. Letters from: Jim Young, Elise White, Elfrida Novak, A. Moore, Valerie Warren, J.Y. Gillies, V.G. Chubak, William E. White, J.S. Corrigan, D. Wilson, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - B.C. Harbours Board (Roberts Bank) (3-6) - Statement (photocopy), 1972; F-55-47-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - BI-BQ (4) - Letter. Letters from: Barrey L. Blow, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - CA-CG (5) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Olive G. Clare, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - CH-CN (6) - Letters. Letters from: Yung Kow Chang, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Circular Letters to Cabinet Ministers and Members (6-4) - Letter (photocopy), speech, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - CO-CZ (7) - Letters, form, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - DA-DZ (8) - Letters. Letters from: Doris L. Rick, Jack Diamond, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Elections--Chief Electoral Officer, etc. (9-3) - Letters. Letters from: K.L. Morton, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - FA-FIN (10) - Letters, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences (10-1) - Letters, statement (photocopy), report. Letters from: Pierre Elliott Trudeau, Henry F. Davis, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Finance--Agent General in U.K. (10-5) - Letters. Letters from: M.G. Stirling, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters, plans. Letters from: Amedee de Pompignan, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Finance--Estimates, Office Expenditures, etc. 1972 (10-6) - Letters. Letters from: R.G. McKee, F-55-47-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Health Services and Hospital Insurance--Minister (14-1) - Petition, letters, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Highways--Deputy and Department (15-2) - Lists, letters, telegrams. Letters from: H.T. Miard, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-71)
  - Highways--B.C. Ferries (15-4) - Letters. Letters from: erry Farmer, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - MA-MI (23) - Letters. Letters from: Eric L. Mallet, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Ministers Without Portfolio (23-4) - Letters. Letters from: Grace McCarthy, Isabel P. Dawson, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Municipal Affairs--Minister (24-1) - Letter. Letters from: W.K. Smith, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - O (27). - Letters (photocopies), 1972; F-55-47-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Premier's Office (28-4) - Letters, brief, financial statement. Letters from: Philip Landau, H.B. Simpson, Ursula Surtees, N.P. Casorso, A.M. Bonnell, William Hooson, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Provincial Secretary--B.C. Medical Plan (29-4) - Letters, financial statistics. Letters from: G.A. Stewart, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Provincial Premiers' Conference (29-8) - Letters, telegrams, lists, report. Letters from: Gerald A. Regan, Michael J.L. Kirby, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Recreation and Conservation--Minister (31-1) - Telegrams, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Rehabilitation and Social Improvement--Minister (31-5) - Letters. Letters from: Philip A. Gaglardi, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - RO-RZ (32) - Letter (photocopy), 1972; F-55-47-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - SA-SI (33) - Letter (carbon copy), 1972; F-55-47-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - SK-SZ (34) - Letters, telegram. Letters from: Frank Richter, Bob Stuebby, Avery S. King, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, policy statement (photocopy), 1972; F-55-47-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Surrey Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (34-8) - Letters. Letters from: Myrtle E. Evertt, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - WA-WZ (37) - Letter. Letters from: G.H. Wheaton, 1972; F-55-47-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - File Lists - Photocopies (originals at Provincial Archives of British Columbia), 1958 - 1969; F-55-47-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
- Federal-Provincial Conferences, 1963 - 1971; F-55-48; 22 cm of textual records
  Records consists of records relating to Federal-Provincial Conferences. Included are summaries of proceedings, working papers, memoranda, correspondence, reports and draft agreements.
  - Constitutional Conference - Reports on discussions, 1963; F-55-48-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences - Summary of proceedings, memoranda, letters. Letters from: Lionel Chevrier, J.E.G. Hardy, 1964; F-55-48-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-72)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences - Lists, itinerary, summary of proceedings, 1964; F-55-48-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences - Draft of act, lists, summary of proceedings, 1964; F-55-48-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Amendment of the Constitution of Canada - Report, letter. Letters from: J.E.G. Hardy, 1965; F-55-48-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences--Volume I - Summary of proceedings, 1965; F-55-48-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences--Volume II - Summary of proceedings, 1965; F-55-48-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences - Summary of proceedings, 1966; F-55-48-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-73)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences - Background papers, opening statements, 1967; F-55-48-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Federal-Provincial Conference on Housing and Urban Development - Summary of proceedings, 1967; F-55-48-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Constitutional Conference - Briefing material, 1969; F-55-48-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Constitutional Conference - Working papers, summary of proceedings, 1969; F-55-48-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Constitutional Conference - Draft provisions of agreement, summary of proceedings, 1971; F-55-48-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
- Premier's subject files, 1939 - 1972; F-55-49; 1.08 m of textual records
  Series consists of subject files compiled by W.A.C. Bennett on various topics. Also included are reports and reference materials related to hydroelectric power in the Peace River and Columbia River regions. Included are charts, correspondence, briefs, financial statistics, estimates, budgets, press releases, reports, financial statistics, minutes, a contract (draft), nomination receipts, policy statements, a bond, payroll forms, expense vouchers, a lease and Statements of Votes.
  The archivist added files 46 to 98 to this series in 2007 after making an appraisal of the material collected from Bennett's home at the time of the original donation. This material had been stored in the Archives but had not been previously processed or included in the Finding Aid.
  - Budget Speech - Charts, 1939 - 1951; F-55-49-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Drug Problem - Letters. Letters from: Eric Martin, Paul Martin. (File probably kept in Premier's safe.), 1952; F-55-49-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Empire Mills - Letters, telegram, brief, printed material. Letters from: E.E. Protheroe. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1952; F-55-49-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-74)
  - Expenditures--Payments to Municipalities - Financial statistics, letter. Letters from: E.L. Harrison, 1967; F-55-49-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Expenditures--Payments to Municipalities - Financial statistics, 1967; F-55-49-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Expenditures--Payments to Municipalities - Financial statistics, 1972; F-55-49-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance - Letter, chart, estimates, budgets, 1965 - 1969; F-55-49-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance - List, map, financial statistics, press release, report, 1965 - 1971; F-55-49-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance--Interim Financial Statements, 1954; F-55-49-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance--Interim Financial Statements, 1965 - 1971; F-55-49-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance--Interim Financial Statements, 1968 - 1971; F-55-49-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance--Interim Financial Statements, 1968 - 1971; F-55-49-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Finance--Revenues and Expenditures - Financial statistics, 1945 - 1951; F-55-49-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - Fort St. James - Letters, itinerary, article. Letters from: L.J. Wallace, 1968; F-55-49-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - J. Gordon Gibson - Report, campaign letter, file note, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-75)
  - International Joint Commission--Libby Dam, Confidential - Letters, reports, minutes. Letters from: A.G.L. McNaughton. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1951 - 1954; F-55-49-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - International Joint Commission--A.G.L. McNaughton - Draft of proposal, letters, telegrams, pamphlet. Letters from: E.M. Sutherland, Lester B. Pearson. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1951 - 1954; F-55-49-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Italy Trip - Letters, financial statistics. Letters from: J.W. Russell, G.G. Crean, 1965; F-55-49-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Joint Northwest Development Committee - Reports, minutes, letters. Letters from: W.W. Foster. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1951 - 1954; F-55-49-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Lion's Gate Bridge - Financial statements, letters, draft of contract. Letters from: J.V. Fisher, Einar M. Gunderson. (File designated "Premier's Safe"; file opened Jan. 1955.), 1952 - 1955; F-55-49-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Nomination Receipts, 1952 - 1972; F-55-49-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Oil Pipeline - Maps, letters, briefs, memoranda, policy statements, submissions. (File designated "Premier's Safe"). Letters from: Frank M. McMahon, 1952; F-55-49-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Ottawa Trip - Letters, financial statistics, newsletter. Letters from: William Clancey, L.J. Wallace, E.J. Benson, Donald L. Brothers, I. Cowan, John E. Wiley, 1969; F-55-49-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - P.G.E. Railway - Letters, telegrams, memoranda, lists, file notes. Letters from: John S. Burton, John Hart, B.E. Valde, Ralph Chetwynd, J.M. Stewart, A.C. Egan, W.I. Anderson, A.J. Brine, M. Robinson, R.M. Burns. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1953; F-55-49-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - P.G.E. Railway - Letters, bond, maps, plans, memorandum, financial statistics, draft of document. Letters from: J.V. Fisher, Ralph Chetwynd. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1942 - 1959; F-55-49-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - P.G.E. Railway Trip - Maps, F-55-49-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-76)
  - Peace File - Telegrams, letters, petition. Letters from: N.A. Pritchard, Olive Trancher, Arthur Stratton, Dorothy McVey, Alec Bell, Nina Freeman, Edith Hutton, 1958; F-55-49-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Payroll - Lists, forms, 1964 - 1965; F-55-49-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Payroll - Lists, forms, 1966 - 1969; F-55-49-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Travel Expenses - Forms, vouchers, cheque stubs, 1959 - 1962; F-55-49-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Travel Expenses - Forms, vouchers, cheque stubs, 1962 - 1964; F-55-49-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Travel Expenses - Forms, vouchers, cheque stubs, 1964 - 1968; F-55-49-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Premier's Office--Travel Expenses - Forms, vouchers, cheque stubs, 1968 - 1972; F-55-49-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-77)
  - Press Releases, 1966 - 1971; F-55-49-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Salary File - Memoranda, 1965 - 1972; F-55-49-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Seaview Apartments - Lease. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1952; F-55-49-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Session--1972. - Note, letters, pamphlets, F-55-49-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Social Credit Convention - Letters, financial statistics, pamphlet, questionnaire, brochure. Letters from: Lazelle Charlie, R.C. Kenmuir, Art Murray, 1968; F-55-49-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Statements of Votes, 1966; F-55-49-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Statements of Votes, 1968 - 1969; F-55-49-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Statements of Votes, 1969; F-55-49-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Summary of Votes, 1969; F-55-49-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Unfavourable Letters - Letter. Letters from: J.H. Neeland. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1952; F-55-49-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Ventures Limited - Letter. Letters from: T. Lindley, 1954; F-55-49-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Dr. William K. Waller - Memorandum, document, statement, 1955; F-55-49-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 55-78)
  - Report on the Columbia and Peace Power Projects, 31 July 1961; F-55-49-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 55-98)